<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BhiwaniTravels</string>

    <string name="tab1">Attractions</string>
    <string name="tab2">Shop</string>
    <string name="tab3">Institutes</string>
    <string name="tab4">About</string>


    <string name="welcome">Welcome To Bhiwani Tour Guide App!</string>


    <string name="attractname1">Sun City Cinemas</string>
    <string name="attractdesc1">Sun City is a mall situated near Huda Park Road, Patel Nagar, Bhiwani.
        It is famous for its food court and cinema theatre.
    </string>
    <string name="attractname2">Vatika Bar and Food Restaurant</string>
    <string name="attractdesc2">It is a resto-cum-bar situated at Housing Board Colony, Near Court, Bhiwani.
        It has a really nice ambience and is famous for Chinese food specially.
    </string>
    <string name="attractname3">Bheem Stadium</string>
    <string name="attractdesc3">This stadium is situated at Housing Board Colony, Bhiwani.
        The most famous place where you\'ll find many new upcoming sportsmen doing their daily practice.
    </string>
    <string name="attractname4">Jat Dharamshala</string>
    <string name="attractdesc4">This is situated near Vaish College, Bhiwani.
        You can book these huge halls at affordable prices as this is not just a place for tourists but also famous for its Banquet, Birthday Parties, Community and Marriage Halls.
    </string>
    <string name="attractname5">Mini Zoo</string>
    <string name="attractdesc5">It is situated at Indira Nagar, Huda Park Road, Bhiwani. It is established with a view to achieve conservation education.
        School field trips are organized here to teach them about species.
    </string>


    <string name="instname1">The Technological Institute Of Textiles And Sciences College</string>
    <string name="instdesc1">This coleege is situated at Birla Colony, Bhiwani.
        It\'s aim is high quality technical education and practical expertise.
        It has served the industry for more than 70 Years and continues to do so.
    </string>
    <string name="instname2">Bhiwani Public School</string>
    <string name="instdesc2">It is situated at Bhiwani - Hansi Road, Park Colony, Vijay Nagar, Bhiwani.
        It is an English Medium Co-Educational Senior Secondary School affiliated to CBSE.
    </string>
    <string name="instname3">Women Police Station</string>
    <string name="instdesc3">It is situated near Police Lines Residential Area.</string>
    <string name="instname4">Chaudhary Bansi Lal University</string>
    <string name="instdesc4">It is situated at B T M Colony, Opposite-Education Board, Bhiwani.
        It is a state university established in 2014 that offers postgraduate courses in various disciplines.
    </string>


    <string name="shopname1">Eaza Restaurant</string>
    <string name="shopdesc1">It is situated at State Highway 14, Near Adarsh College, Bhiwani.
        It is a family restaurant famous for it\'s mouth-watering South Indian Food.</string>
    <string name="shopname2">Much More Footwear</string>
    <string name="shopdesc2">It is situated at Naya Bazar, Housing Board Colony, Bhiwani.
        It is a top company in the category of Shoe Dealers, also known for Women Shoe Dealers, Shoe Material Dealers and much more.
    </string>
    <string name="shopname3">Chatpati Chaap Restaurant</string>
    <string name="shopdesc3">It is situated near Bank of Baroda, Impromant Market, Opposite to shop no. 2.
        It sells best Chaap across the place at really decent price which is why you\'ll never find this place empty.
    </string>
    <string name="shopname4">Lakshmi Bikaner Misthan Bhandar</string>
    <string name="shopdesc4">It is situated at SH 14, Naya Bazaar, Housing Board Colony, Bhiwani.
        It sells the best sweets and gujrati dish \'Dhokla\'. It also takes contract offers.
    </string>
    <string name="shopname5">China Town</string>
    <string name="shopdesc5">It is situated at Krishna Colony, Bhiwani. If you are a fast food lover, then this is the perfect place for you.
        It has a vast variety of fast food restaurants and eating joints. There\'s nothing that you will fail to find here.
    </string>
    <string name="shopname6">Hari Collection</string>
    <string name="shopdesc6">It is situated at Krishna Colony, Bhiwani. It is one of the best place to shop for trending dresses and suits at reasonable prices.</string>

    <string name="madeby">Developed by: Yashika Kalra</string>
    <string name="describe">Hello, Welcome to Bhiwani, also known as \'Choti Kashi\'. If you love spicy food and love to travel to religious places,
        this is the place you must visit. So, don\'t wait add this place to your dream places right now. :p\n\n

        Bhiwani is a city and a municipal council in Bhiwani district in the state of Haryana, India.
        Besides being a seat of spiritual learning, the city is at the centre of regional politics and hometown of three former Haryana chief ministers:
        Bansi Lal, Banarsi Dass Gupta and Hukum Singh.\n\n

        As of 2001 India census, Bhiwani had a population of 1634445. Males constitute 54% of the population and females 46%.
        Bhiwani has an average literacy rate of 69%, higher than the national average of 59.5%; with male literacy of 76% and female literacy of 62%.
        13% of the population is under 7 years of age.\n
    </string>


</resources>
